allnurses.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy - Site Center - allnurses

allnurses.com, INC ("us", "we", or "our") operates the allnurses.com website, the store.allnurses.com website, the marketplace.allnurses.com website, and the jobs.allnurses.com website (each one individually and collectively the 'Service'). 

Your privacy on this site is of the utmost importance to us. We want to make your experience exploring our site satisfying while protecting your privacy. 

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. 

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service. 

##  Definitions 

**Service**

Service means the allnurses.com website, the store.allnurses.com website the marketplace.allnurses.com website, the jobs.allnurses.com website and the allnurses.com mobile application operated by allnurses.com, INC 

**Personal Data**

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession). 

**Usage Data**

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit). 

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device). 

**Data Controller**

Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. 

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data. 

**Data Processors (or Service Providers)**

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. 

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively. 

**Data Subject (or User)**

Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data. 

##  Information Collection And Use 

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you. 

###  Types of Data Collected 

####  Personal Data 

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: 

  * Email address 
  * Cookies and Usage Data 
  * Date of Birth 
  * State and Country 
  * Education 
  * Occupation 
  * Years of Experience 
  * Other data that is voluntarily offered 

We may use your Personal Data to improve your experience on the site or to send email, newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send. 

####  Usage Data 

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data"). 

This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. 

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. 

##  Use of Data 

allnurses.com, INC uses the collected data for various purposes: 

  * To provide and maintain our Service 
  * To notify you about changes to our Service 
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so 
  * To provide customer support 
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service 
  * To monitor the usage of our Service 
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues 
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information 

##  Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), allnurses.com, INC's legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it. 

allnurses.com, INC may process your Personal Data because: 

  * We need to perform a contract with you 
  * You have given us permission to do so 
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights 
  * For payment processing purposes 
  * To comply with the law 

##  Retention of Data 

allnurses.com, INC will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. 

allnurses.com, INC will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods. 

##  Transfer Of Data 

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those in your jurisdiction. 

If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the United States and process it there. 

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

allnurses.com, INC will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information. 

##  Disclosure Of Data 

###  Legal Requirements 

allnurses.com, INC may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

  * To comply with a legal obligation 
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of allnurses.com, INC 
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service 
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public 
  * To protect against legal liability 

##  Security Of Data 

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

##  "Do Not Track" Signals 

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. 

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser. 

##  Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. allnurses.com, INC aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. 

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. 

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights: 

**The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.  **Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you. 

**The right of rectification.**  You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete. 

**The right to object.**  You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data. 

**The right of restriction.**  You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information. 

**The right to data portability.  **You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format. 

**The right to withdraw consent.**  You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where allnurses.com, INC relied on your consent to process your personal information. 

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. 

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA). 

##  Service Providers 

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. 

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. 

###  Advertising 

We use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Service. These companies may place cookies or use your IP address or other aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number), about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

Google/DoubleClick Cookie 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other websites on the Internet. 

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>

More information on how Google uses this information can be found at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>. 

###  Behavioral Remarketing 

allnurses.com, INC uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service. 

Google AdWords 

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. 

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> \- for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. 

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

AppNexus 

AppNexus remarketing service is provided by AppNexus Inc. 

You can opt-out of AppNexus remarketing by visiting the Privacy the AppNexus Platform web page: <http://www.appnexus.com/platform-policy#choices>

For more information on the privacy practices of AppNexus, please visit the AppNexus Platform Privacy Policy web page: <http://www.appnexus.com/platform-policy/>

###  Payments 

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors). 

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information. 

The payment processors we work with are: 

PayPal 

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

##  Links To Other Sites 

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. 

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. 

We participate in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and other affiliated sites. We choose affiliate links carefully in order to provide an opportunity for you to support allnurses.com. 

##  Children's Privacy 

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children"). 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. 

##  Changes To This Privacy Policy 

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. 

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. 

##  Contact Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

Via our Help Desk: <https://allnurses.com/contact/>

Or by mail: 

allnurses.com INC  
c/o Privacy Policy  
7900 International Dr #300,  
Bloomington MN 55425
